Today, we have two guests from Ochanouma, Mr. Cirella Yonemura and Mr. Tashiros Mir, on TV Aichi!
Hello everyone. We are Ochanouma.
I'm Kirera Yonemura from Aichi prefecture.
I am Tashiros Mir from Kanagawa prefecture.
I'm Tashiros Mir from Kanagawa Prefecture.
It's been a year in July since your debut.
Wow, how do you feel? As otaku, we are all feeling that it's already been a year,
I am sure that some of you are thinking, "It's already been a year," and some of you are thinking, "It's only been a year,
What do you think?
We also feel like it's already been a year, and we also feel like it's only been a year.
I also feel like it's only been a year,
But I also feel like it's been a long time.
Looking back on it, I feel like it was a long time.
But from the very beginning, you all had flowers and a strong presence,
I didn't feel like a newcomer at all,
I feel very strongly that only one year has passed.
Since the group was originally formed from trainees, I think there are probably many people who feel that way.
Do you feel that anything has changed after a year?
When Rocco and the others joined the group, they were quite puppy-like.
Recently, they have become rebellious and are getting more aggressive.
I think you can feel that in their performances.
You can feel it.
His passion is growing.
As a human being?
Yes, as a human being.
You are growing.
I think you have a famous address, including me.
I see.
I'm sure you have fond memories of each song,
Do you have any particular favorite part of this song?
May I ask something from you, Mr. Yonemura?
I am a little emotionally anxious, like the a cappella nesson between Chain Girl and Tamako Misaki at the beginning of "Summer.
I really like this part.
It's great.
It really made my skin crawl.
They are both great singers,Because they both have amazing singing voices,
I want people from all walks of life to listen to their voices alone.
I can feel that the music that Kamie Hirose put out is included in this album.
I feel it a lot.
From the moment I heard the lyrics, I thought it was a song by Kamie Hirose.
So I wondered how to make the recording a tea-blind song.
While thinking about it, yes, I did. I did it.
The music video really conveys a sense of fun, doesn't it?
Yes, it is.
The music video was very cold. That day.
I thought so.
But the costumes were of the highest quality,
We could all shake in the cold.
Yes, we did. We filmed it.
But it doesn't show in your facial expression at all?
No, only when we were spinning.
It's over now.
The shoulder is shaking.
I love that this is your last summer.
Thank you very much.
Summer. It's already my voice as it is.
It's nice, isn't it? It's nice, isn't it? It's summery.
It's summery.
The scene where the three of us are playing cards.
There was a scene where the three of us are playing cards.
I thought it looked like a lot of fun.
I felt like it really brought out everyone's true expressions,
You mean you actually filmed the scene while playing cards?
Yes, we did,
But some of the cards were missing,
I was playing bouncing cards all the time,
I was playing bouncing cards all the time, but I ended up here.
I was missing some cards, and I was playing bouncing key all the time. I was bouncing around the cards for a long time, but I ended up here.
I see.
Wow.
I didn't finish.It didn't end.
But I felt like I could watch everyone playing together in such a friendly manner for a long time,
I enjoyed the music video from various angles, as well as the way everyone was making decisions, and the expressions from various angles.
Thank you very much.
I was really enjoying the expressions from various angles in the music video, which was a bit like a continuation of the music video. I'd like to know.
First of all, the first part of the song is "Yay! The first part of the song is "Yay!
I'd like everyone to get really excited at that part, too.
For example, if you have a towel, you can wave it,
If you can say "whoo" with me, I think you can get excited from the very beginning.
It's a nostalgic feeling, isn't it?
I think this song will be used at idol events in Taiwan.
Yes, I think so. I'm really looking forward to hearing more of it in the field.
Yes, I am. I will do my best.
What kind of songs do you like, Mr. Tashiro?
My song is called "Ocha no mama horo bykuin no ichiban ni yori yori wa chabacha" (The Life of a Tea Bike Inn is More Than a Burning Bike Inn),
I think the cool dance scene of the members in this song is very attractive,
The most memorable moment for me was during the dance lesson,
I remember one of the most memorable moments was during a dance lesson, there is a count called "Kecak part",
I remember one of the memorable dance scenes was during a dance lesson, there was a count called "Kecak Part".
Momoko Kitahara became Momoko Kitahara-sama,
Momoko Kitahara becomes Momoko Kitahara-sama, and everyone does Kecak.
That part really left an impression on me,
It's something that hasn't been done in any of the previous tea ceremonies,
I hope you will enjoy it.
I hope you enjoy it. It's a very Kitahara world, isn't it?
The feeling.
The world is amazing.
It is both fantastic and mysterious.
It's a lemon, or rather, the finished soundtrack.
When the sound source first came to us, it was the right choice.
We were lemoning ourselves,
I thought, "Wow, this is a peach.
And today's costume.
Yes. That's right.
The costumes.
First it was a dripping costume, and then you changed it to the current costume,The change from the initial shizuku-like outfit to the current outfit,
I wonder if it means something a bit like the future.
Mr. Kitahara suggested that the tea be left as it was in the future,
Then the scene turned out to be like this, with everyone in these costumes,
That's probably it.
I was thinking about it a lot, and I wondered what it meant.
But the people who are doing it don't think about it.
Is that so?
Now that you mention it, yes.
I thought about it a lot, and listened to it again,
I was thinking about the lyrics, and thinking about how good they are,
I'm listening to the song again, thinking about how good the lyrics are, and wondering where the "tea leaves" are for me.
I'm so happy.
I'm so excited.
I'm really excited.
This time there are four songs,
I think I can bring you a lot more variety of "just as tea",
How do you like it?
Yes, each of the four songs is filled with various kinds of tea,
No two songs are the same,
If you can get this syncre, I think you will be able to understand the current charm of Ocha-no-Mama,
I hope you will get it.
This is the first 4-song cart music video single as Ochanomama,
It is really a single with a lot of things to offer,
I think you can enjoy various kinds of Ocha-no-Mama in each song,
I hope you will enjoy listening to the various songs depending on your mood.
Thank you very much.
From here, I would like to see some parts of you two that I have not shown so far by taking a psychological test,
I would like to start with the psychological test.
Was it actually not a poisoned apple that Snow White accidentally ate?
What do you think she ate?
1. strawberry
Momo (momo)
3. grapefruit
4. feast4. feast
5. momo
Well, let's start with you, Shashiro-san.
Ichigo.
I can see what's wrong with you.
Huh?
It was a problem.
You chose the road, and the part of you that is not good-looking is your small-mindedness.
That's right.
You are sensitive and small-minded.
You can't act unless you are with everyone else, or you worry about what others think of you,
Maybe you should try to act boldly without thinking too much.
You are right.
I'm very anxious.
I think a lot.
I had a fortune-telling reading once,
I even had a fortune-telling session once, and the advice I received was that I would be better off if I went further ahead,
I don't know.
I'm serious,
I don't care.
So you are not the type of person who stands out in front of others?
Yes, I guess so. She is quite reserved.
That's for sure.
If she talks, she talks,
You don't mind? I have a personality,
But I do have that personality.
Wow...
You're right.
You don't go out alone?
Lately I've been doing my best to do so,
I couldn't do it in the past,
But recently I'm able to go out to eat alone in my free time.
That's great.
Do you have a desire to be more out in front?
Is that about right?Is that about right?
Ever since I was little, I have always wanted to be in the forefront,
Even at playdates, I would try to play roles that no one else was playing,
I would even think of choreography,
I was a very forward child,
So I definitely have that personality somewhere in me.
Wow, that's amazing.
Then, Shiho Shibata is a bit of a deep silk this time.
The deep part.
Then, Yonemura-san, you are Peach.
Yes.
If you chose "peach," you are a little selfish.
You are right.
You are a spoiled brat and a bit selfish.
If you don't get your way, you turn into a moody pot,
You don't keep your promises to your friends when you change your mind in the middle of a meeting,
Before you get in my face, let's end this patience thing a little at a time.
It's true.
Seriously?
I don't have an image of that at all.
I'm pretty selfish myself,
If something bad comes out.
I'm in a bad mood.
Like this.
I see.
So if you look closely, you might be able to get a sense of that from our point of view.
I think we can sense it.
I want to see it!
Wow, that's a bit...
That's a bit...
It's difficult.
I forgive you.
I'll take it.
Now, the last problem.
I have prepared a question about tea, since it is tea time.
On a quiet day, I would like to read a book, listen to my favorite music, or do something I enjoy while drinking tea.On a quiet day, I would like to read a book, listen to my favorite music, or do something I enjoy while sipping a cup of tea.
Which cup would you use to drink tea?
1. A small ceramic teacup.
A beautifully patterned teacup.
A slightly larger mug.
I would be 1.
I guess I am 2.
This question shows what you value in life.
Big! It's a lot of hope!
The person who chose number 1, Mr. Yonemura, is the type of person who finds happiness in ordinary life.
He is the type of person who creates peace and tranquility in his life.
A small cup of tea in a teapot will soon be gone.
And making tea in a teapot takes a lot of time and effort.
A person who enjoys such time and effort.
Finding peace in your ordinary life is how you enjoy your life.
Peaceful, do-nothing time.
I love it.
I prefer to do nothing.
I would rather spend my time quietly than going out and having a good time.
I don't want to do anything so much that I think sleeping would be a better use of my time.
I don't want to do much. I have a very bright image,
On my days off, I'd like to be involved with other people, go out, and chat.
Lately it's been really bad.
I sleep all the time.
I see.
In that sense, I guess I am right.
Do you like to put in the time and effort? It's a pain in the ass.
It's a lot of trouble.
It's like the room isn't. It's really a deathly hassle.
It's not really a hassle to death,
I might like that kind of hassle.
Do you like detailed work?
Yes, I do.
I love teak people.
Then you may be right.
Mr. Tashiba is a beautiful teacup.Tashiba is a beautiful teacup.
The person who chose this one is someone who wants to be surrounded by his/her favorite things that resonate with cheer.
Tea in a teacup is often black tea or herbal tea.
You are a person who loves things that suit your feeling and touch your cheer.
Do you have a sensitive side and your emotions can be greatly affected by small events or interactions with others?
Do you want to be surrounded by things you love in order to stabilize yourself?
You are so right.
I felt a little "wow".
It's an event.
It's a great hobby of yours.
It's amazing. It's true that I'm the kind of person who wants to be surrounded by things that I really like,
My hobbies and interests change from time to time,
It's so annoying that I really want to master that kind of sensibility.
What do you like now?
I like dolls. I like dolls.
I really like rolls,
I like rolls a lot,
I decorate my room with them,
Are they realistic dolls?
I love Barbie dolls.
Hui, yes.
A doll.
She looks like a doll.
I love them so much that lately I've been looking at all kinds of Barbie merchandise and dolls,
I'm kind of addicted to them.
It's very soothing.
I really want to get into what I like,
Once I get into something I really like, I'm really into it.
I thought I could get rid of their personalities.
You were standing up.
You were standing.
Thank you very much.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Do you have a message for everyone?
Yes, I do. This is my second year as a tea ceremony horse, and I would like to keep working hard.Yes, I am. As this is the second year of Ocha-no-Ma, we will continue to work harder and harder.
We will continue to do our best with full spirit and ten members working together. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much.